autotrader.co.za 2019-07-03

# Privacy Policy - AutoTrader

This Privacy Policy must be read in conjunction with our Terms and Conditions

This Policy sets out how we use and protect any personal information that you, the customer, give us when you use our Website. This privacy policy has been put in place to assure you and give you the peace of mind that we take access to your personal information seriously. It also gives you our details in case you want to contact us and query any issues that you may have. If you have any questions about this Policy or do not agree with it, please contact us before using the Website and our services. We may change this Policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure you are happy with any changes.

All details supplied to us by virtue of the Website, any content thereon, or the facility or services offered thereby, will be safeguarded by our privacy policy.

We undertake to use our best endeavours to maintain the privacy of the information you have divulged to us in consequence of utilising the Website. For this purpose, we have taken measures to ensure that information supplied to us is held securely.

As a result, we may occasionally request proof of identity before allowing access to your information.

However, by providing us with your details, you agree to us:

  * utilising your information to communicate further with you in future regarding matters which we believe might be of interest or relevant to you;
  * storing your information in our database for future reference and for purposes of the above; and
  * utilising your information for statistical purposes. 

For the purposes of the prevention or detection of offences, and/or the apprehension or prosecution of offenders, we may share any information obtained or collected by us with the Police, other public or private sector agencies or representative bodies in accordance with the relevant legislation.

This will include public authorities, insurance companies, finance companies, automotive advertising companies and/or other agencies. Information shared in this way will not be used for marketing purposes.

When you register on the Website, we ask you whether you would like to receive our email newsletters detailing changes to the site, offers and services from third party/s that we feel may be of interest to you. You have the ability to opt-out of receiving all or any of these offers during registration.

When you access the Website (directly or indirectly and without necessarily registering thereon) we automatically receive and store information on our server logs from your browser or mobile platform including your cell phone number, location, IP address, Cookie information and the page you requested.

Credit card information is collected over a secure connection. Credit card information is used solely for the purpose of payment processing. We utilize a third party service provider for payment processing, and by providing us with your credit card information, you are giving your consent to us (or a third party nominated by us) to conduct a credit check on you as well as processing the credit card information for the purposes stipulated herein.

We provide or make your personal information available to:

  * Other companies in the Naspers group of companies, details of which are available [here](https://www.naspers.com/), to learn more about our customers and create a more relevant, engaging customer experience.
  * Other parties that provide content, advertising services or functionality on our Platforms, including advertising providers which help us and our advertising customers provide advertisements that are tailored to users’ interests and understand how users respond to these advertisements, audience-measurement companies which help us measure the overall usage of our Platforms and compare that usage with other online services, and social networking services such as Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn and Instagram that enable you to register for and log into some of our services and share things you find on our Platforms with your social network. These third parties may collect or receive information about your use of our Platforms, including through the use of cookies, web beacons and other technologies, and this information may be collected over time and combined with information collected on various websites and online services. We do not control the privacy practices of these or any other third party services and advise you to read the privacy policies of these services before connecting to them.

Amendments and updates to this policy may be made from time to time. Any revisions will be posted on this page and you are urged to familiarise yourself from time to time with the content of this page.
